{
    "subject": "resource/Century_Milstead",
    "predicate": "property/playingTeam",
    "object": "resource/Philadelphia_Quakers_(AFL)",
    "human_readable": "Century Milstead played for the Philadelphia Quakers (AFL).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8854276537895203,
            "question": "What team did Century Milstead play for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8600958585739136,
            "question": "When did Century Milstead play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.856705367565155,
            "question": "Who is Century Milstead?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8339605331420898,
            "question": "What position might Century Milstead have played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8304827809333801,
            "question": "In what league did Century Milstead play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7803465127944946,
            "question": "What sport did Century Milstead likely play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7305715680122375,
            "question": "Was Century Milstead a star player?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4375532567501068,
            "question": "Are there any famous players from the Philadelphia Quakers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33582204580307007,
            "question": "What is the AFL?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19927828013896942,
            "question": "Can you name another AFL player?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Century Milstead played for the Philadelphia Quakers (AFL).",
            "html": "dbpedia_194_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the AFL?",
            "html": "dbpedia_194_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous players from the Philadelphia Quakers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_194_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Century Milstead a star player?",
            "html": "dbpedia_194_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_194_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_194_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_194_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_194_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_194_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_194_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_194_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_194_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_194_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_194_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information that confirms Century Milstead played for the Philadelphia Quakers of the American Football League. Specifically, document #4 and #31 mention that Century Milstead was one of the nine players who had previously played for various National Football League teams and played for the Philadelphia Quakers in 1926, winning the league's only championship."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Century Allen \"Wally\" Milstead, including his professional career which included playing with the Philadelphia Quakers of the American Football League. Therefore, the statement that Century Milstead played for the Philadelphia Quakers (AFL) is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}